{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Faucet \u0026 Plumbing Repair Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40113/":{"taskOID":40113,"originalTaskOID":40113,"setID":424,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":762,"questionDisplayText":"Project Description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the small project? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5194,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Repair a faulty plumbing item","answerDisplayText":"Repair a faulty plumbing item","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3243,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Install a new plumbing item","answerDisplayText":"Install a new plumbing item","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5246,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Replace an old plumbing item","answerDisplayText":"Replace an old plumbing item","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2448,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Find and/or fix a leak","answerDisplayText":"Find and/or fix a leak","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5606,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Several small plumbing 'fix-it' or install projects","answerDisplayText":"Several small plumbing 'fix-it' or install projects","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2487,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Fix noise","answerDisplayText":"Fix noise","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5259,"questionDisplayText":"Plumbing Repairs","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"For repairs, what best describes the problem?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3379,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Item not working properly","answerDisplayText":"Item not working properly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3378,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Item not working at all","answerDisplayText":"Item not working at all","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4208,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"No hot water","answerDisplayText":"No hot water","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2758,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Gas smell","answerDisplayText":"Gas smell","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3511,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Leaking pipe","answerDisplayText":"Leaking pipe","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2668,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Frozen pipe","answerDisplayText":"Frozen pipe","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3376,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Item is loose","answerDisplayText":"Item is loose","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3377,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Item is too tight","answerDisplayText":"Item is too tight","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4797,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Poor water pressure","answerDisplayText":"Poor water pressure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4267,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Noisy pipes","answerDisplayText":"Noisy pipes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2497,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Fixture not draining or flushing","answerDisplayText":"Fixture not draining or flushing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1437,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Clogged/slow drain","answerDisplayText":"Clogged/slow drain","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5260,"questionDisplayText":"Plumbing Fixtures","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"For installs or replacement, which items are needed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1953,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Dishwasher","answerDisplayText":"Dishwasher","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1959,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Disposal","answerDisplayText":"Disposal","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2321,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Exterior faucet","answerDisplayText":"Exterior faucet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2391,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Faucet","answerDisplayText":"Faucet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3289,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Instant hot water dispenser","answerDisplayText":"Instant hot water dispenser","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4691,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Pipe","answerDisplayText":"Pipe","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5648,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Shower drain","answerDisplayText":"Shower drain","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5652,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Shower/Tub","answerDisplayText":"Shower/Tub","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5739,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Sink","answerDisplayText":"Sink","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6423,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Toilet","answerDisplayText":"Toilet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6884,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Water main","answerDisplayText":"Water main","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6890,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Water pressure valve","answerDisplayText":"Water pressure valve","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6949,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Whirlpool tub","answerDisplayText":"Whirlpool tub","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":20001,"questionDisplayText":"After Business Hours","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need help after business hours?","shortQuestionText":"Requires help after business hours?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":762,"questionDisplayText":"Project Description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the small project? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5194,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Repair a faulty plumbing item","answerDisplayText":"Repair a faulty plumbing item","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3243,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Install a new plumbing item","answerDisplayText":"Install a new plumbing item","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5246,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Replace an old plumbing item","answerDisplayText":"Replace an old plumbing item","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2448,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Find and/or fix a leak","answerDisplayText":"Find and/or fix a leak","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5606,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Several small plumbing 'fix-it' or install projects","answerDisplayText":"Several small plumbing 'fix-it' or install projects","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2487,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Fix noise","answerDisplayText":"Fix noise","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5194,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Repair a faulty plumbing item","answerDisplayText":"Repair a faulty plumbing item","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3243,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Install a new plumbing item","answerDisplayText":"Install a new plumbing item","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5246,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Replace an old plumbing item","answerDisplayText":"Replace an old plumbing item","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2448,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Find and/or fix a leak","answerDisplayText":"Find and/or fix a leak","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5606,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Several small plumbing 'fix-it' or install projects","answerDisplayText":"Several small plumbing 'fix-it' or install projects","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2487,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Fix noise","answerDisplayText":"Fix noise","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5259,"questionDisplayText":"Plumbing Repairs","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"For repairs, what best describes the problem?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3379,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Item not working properly","answerDisplayText":"Item not working properly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3378,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Item not working at all","answerDisplayText":"Item not working at all","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4208,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"No hot water","answerDisplayText":"No hot water","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2758,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Gas smell","answerDisplayText":"Gas smell","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3511,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Leaking pipe","answerDisplayText":"Leaking pipe","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2668,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Frozen pipe","answerDisplayText":"Frozen pipe","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3376,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Item is loose","answerDisplayText":"Item is loose","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3377,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Item is too tight","answerDisplayText":"Item is too tight","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4797,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Poor water pressure","answerDisplayText":"Poor water pressure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4267,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Noisy pipes","answerDisplayText":"Noisy pipes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2497,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Fixture not draining or flushing","answerDisplayText":"Fixture not draining or flushing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1437,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Clogged/slow drain","answerDisplayText":"Clogged/slow drain","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3379,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Item not working properly","answerDisplayText":"Item not working properly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3378,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Item not working at all","answerDisplayText":"Item not working at all","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4208,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"No hot water","answerDisplayText":"No hot water","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2758,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Gas smell","answerDisplayText":"Gas smell","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3511,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Leaking pipe","answerDisplayText":"Leaking pipe","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2668,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Frozen pipe","answerDisplayText":"Frozen pipe","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3376,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Item is loose","answerDisplayText":"Item is loose","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3377,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Item is too tight","answerDisplayText":"Item is too tight","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4797,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Poor water pressure","answerDisplayText":"Poor water pressure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4267,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Noisy pipes","answerDisplayText":"Noisy pipes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2497,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Fixture not draining or flushing","answerDisplayText":"Fixture not draining or flushing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1437,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Clogged/slow drain","answerDisplayText":"Clogged/slow drain","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5260,"questionDisplayText":"Plumbing Fixtures","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"For installs or replacement, which items are needed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1953,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Dishwasher","answerDisplayText":"Dishwasher","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1959,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Disposal","answerDisplayText":"Disposal","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2321,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Exterior faucet","answerDisplayText":"Exterior faucet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2391,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Faucet","answerDisplayText":"Faucet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3289,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Instant hot water dispenser","answerDisplayText":"Instant hot water dispenser","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4691,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Pipe","answerDisplayText":"Pipe","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5648,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Shower drain","answerDisplayText":"Shower drain","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5652,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Shower/Tub","answerDisplayText":"Shower/Tub","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5739,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Sink","answerDisplayText":"Sink","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6423,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Toilet","answerDisplayText":"Toilet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6884,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Water main","answerDisplayText":"Water main","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6890,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Water pressure valve","answerDisplayText":"Water pressure valve","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6949,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Whirlpool tub","answerDisplayText":"Whirlpool tub","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":1953,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Dishwasher","answerDisplayText":"Dishwasher","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1959,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Disposal","answerDisplayText":"Disposal","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2321,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Exterior faucet","answerDisplayText":"Exterior faucet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2391,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Faucet","answerDisplayText":"Faucet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3289,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Instant hot water dispenser","answerDisplayText":"Instant hot water dispenser","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4691,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Pipe","answerDisplayText":"Pipe","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5648,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Shower drain","answerDisplayText":"Shower drain","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5652,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Shower/Tub","answerDisplayText":"Shower/Tub","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5739,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Sink","answerDisplayText":"Sink","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6423,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Toilet","answerDisplayText":"Toilet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6884,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Water main","answerDisplayText":"Water main","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6890,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Water pressure valve","answerDisplayText":"Water pressure valve","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6949,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Whirlpool tub","answerDisplayText":"Whirlpool tub","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":20001,"questionDisplayText":"After Business Hours","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need help after business hours?","shortQuestionText":"Requires help after business hours?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40113/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40113,"taskName":"Faucets, Fixtures and Pipes - Repair or Replace","taskDescription":"Install, Repair or Replace Plumbing or Fixtures","xmTaskDescriptor":"Faucet \u0026 Plumbing Repair Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":317,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Faucet Fixture Pipe toilet sink","textMessagingName":"Plumbing Fixtures","rolloverLongDesc":"Main category for plumbing that includes everything but drain clearing, gas work \u0026 those installations that are done in conjunction with remodeling \u0026 construction. Includes installations of such items as a wet bar or laundry sink that are not being done as part of a larger remodeling project.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes toilets, sinks, faucets, pipes, etc.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install, Repair or Replace Plumbing or Fixtures.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Faucet \u0026 Plumbing Repair \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Kitchen, Shower \u0026 Bath Faucet Repair | Fix Pipes","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":60,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Faucets, Fixtures and Pipe Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Faucets, Fixtures and Pipes - Repair or Replace","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Faucets, Fixture \u0026 Pipe Project","urlName":"Faucets-Fixtures-and-Pipes-Repair-or-Replace","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Faucet \u0026 Plumbing Repair Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Kitchen, Shower \u0026 Bath Faucet Repair, Costs, Reviews","searchKeywords":"toilet, sink, bathtub, shower, bathroom, plumber, sewer, laundry, kitchen, wet bar plumbing, plumbers, drip, leak, vanity, spigot, valve","emcCategoryOid":-12058,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":424,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false}}